There are among us a people,
我们之中有一个民族
gifted with a perfect memory  of all their past lives.
他们对前世的生活有着完美的记忆
They call themselves  Infinites.
他们称自己为无限
Among the Infinites,  two groups have vied for power.
在无限一族之中，有两个集团在争夺权力
On one side the Believers,
其中一方   是信徒们
dedicated  to using their knowledge
他们致力于使用世代传承的知识
for the protection and growth  of all humanity.
为全人类的发展保驾护航
Against them  stand the Nihilists,
与他们作对的另一方  则是一群虚无主义者
who see this power  as a curse.
他们认为这种超能力是一种诅咒
New technologies  have given the Nihilists
新的高科技给虚无主义者
an opportunity  to end all life on earth.
拥有了消灭地球上所有生命的机会
And the race is on  for its control.
争夺控制权的竞赛开始了
Treadway,  tell me you got it.
崔德维，告诉我你拿到了
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.  I got it.
是的  是的，我拿到了 我拿到它了
Might be delayed a little.  I'm headed to meet you now.
可能会迟一点 我现在就去见你
Copy that.
收到
Treadway, you okay?
崔德维   你还好吗?
We can't let them  get the Egg back.
我们不能让他们把蛋拿回去
I can't believe  Bathurst would go this far.
真不敢相信巴瑟斯特会这么做
He's not the man  we remember.
他已经不是我们记忆中的那个人了
Shit.
该死的
Abel.  I'm gonna take a shortcut.  Meet me at the freeway.
亚伯  我要走捷径 在高速公路上见
They got it blocked off.
他们封锁了公路
Get to the base of the crane. Treadway, listen.
到起重机下面去     ---崔德维   听着
Do not go up that bridge.
千万别上那座桥
Treadway? Treadway?
崔德维?  崔德维?
Abel, listen to me.
亚伯，听我说
If I fail, look inside.
如果我失败了，看里面
I don't know what miracle  you think you're gonna pull off,
我不知道你会创造什么奇迹
but there's a 150-foot gap  in front of you.
但你面前有150英尺长的断头路
What is his plan?
他的计划是什么?
Leona. Please.
丽安娜 求求你
Leona, wake up.  Wake up.
丽安娜, 醒醒   快醒醒
I'll find you  in the Beginning.
我会在一开始找到你
I love you.
我爱你
Did you ever have  a dream so real  it felt like a memory?
你有没有做过如此真实的梦，就像回忆一样?
You ever catch yourself  in the mirror  and it's a surprise?
你有没有在镜子前看着自己，然后觉得很惊讶?
Like you expected to see  someone else's face
就像你期望看到别人的脸  凝视着你
All these people  all going somewhere,  all doing something.
所有的人 所有的物  所有的事
But what does it all add up to?
这所有的一切说明了什么
Maybe if I knew the answer,  all the little things  might click together.
也许我知道答案 也许把所有的小事情凑在一起后
They might make sense.
才能找到答案
Hey. Hi. Evan. Right on time.
嘿       ---埃文   很准时嘛
Nice to see you.  How are ya?
很高兴见到你   你好吗？
Any trouble getting here?No. No, not at all.
有什么麻烦吗？  --- 不  不 一点也没有
Okay.
好吧
Third interview this week.
本周的第三次面试
Here he is. Hey, gentlemen.
他来了   ---嘿  绅士们
Hey. How are you?
嘿 你好吗?
Pleasure to meet you.Evan, great to meet you.
很高兴见到你   ---埃文，很高兴见到你
Thank you so much  for your time.  I really appreciate it.
非常感谢您抽出时间    我真的很感激
Wow. Beautiful place  you have here.Thank you.
哇   你这地方真漂亮    ---谢谢你！
Absolutely gorgeous.I just got a couple questions  if you don't mind.
太漂亮了  ---如果你不介意的话，我有几个问题要问
Yeah, of course.
是的    当然
There are a couple  of question marks  in your past.
我对你的简历有点疑问
I recognize that.
我知道
You're the first face  people see
你是客人们走进我的餐厅时 看到的第一张脸
And they'd be greeted  with a smile.
所以要面带微笑迎接客人
I have had some issues  in the past.
我的简历是有一些问题
I did  a full background check  on you, Mr. McCauley.
我对你做了个全面的背景调查，麦考利先生
I spoke to some  of your past employers.
我和你以前的雇主谈过
And you know what?  They all said  the same thing.
你知道吗? 他们都说了同样的话
I'm interested to hear  what they had to say.
我很想听听他们是怎么说的
They say you're great!
他们说你很棒!
They say you're smart.  He's a smart guy.
他们说你很聪明     他是个聪明的家伙
Smart guy right here, huh?
聪明蛋就在这里  哈
That's all good.  I guess I've got the job then.  When do I start?
这太好了  我想我得到这份工作了  我什么时候开始上班?
Tell me about the customer  you attacked.
跟我说说你袭击过的那个顾客
He assaulted a waitress.
他袭击了一名女服务员
So you broke his arm.
所以你打断了他的胳膊
I did.  It was unintentional.
是的，但我不是故意的
Excuse me,  but he grabbed her ass.
不好意思，他抓了她的屁股
I asked him to leave politely.
我礼貌地请他离开
He put his hands on me.  No charges were ever filed.  Everything was dismissed.
他把手放在我身上   一句话也不说   然后就完事了
So you just walked out  of a shift at Locanda  and you-- you never came back?
所以你就直接下班 并且再也没有回去了?
I had a personal issue.  That was six years ago.
我有个私人问题   那是六年前的事了
Yeah, your manager told me  that you were institutionalized.
你的经理告诉我你被送进了精神病院
For two weeks.
两个星期而已
Two weeks.  Melanie, it's just two weeks.  Just two weeks.
两个星期    梅拉尼   才两个星期而已  才两个星期
Look. My struggles  with mental illness  are a part of my past.
瞧  与精神疾病做斗争 是我的一段经历
I haven't had so much  as an eye twitch since.
从那以后 我再也没有犯过病了
I think, if anything, getting  through what I've been through  only makes me stronger.
我觉得，如果说有什么区别的话，那就是这些经历会让我更坚强
And I am 100% confident  in my ability to manage here.
我对自己的管理能力有100%的信心
Thanks for coming in today,  Evan.
谢谢你今天能来，埃文
Please. Look, I know  what it looks like.
听着，我知道这套说辞代表着什么
But my illness isn't an issue  you have to worry about.
你们不需要担心我的病
I promise you--Hey, we'll be  in touch, okay?
我向你们保证    ---嘿  保持联系 ，好吗?
No, you won't.
不,  你不会的
Excuse me?
你说什么?
I know the brush-off  when I hear it.
我知道你是在拒绝我
Mr. McCauley,  you are clearly awesome  at dealing with conflict.
麦考利先生，你显然很擅长处理冲突
You have no idea.
你肯定想象不出来
Thanks for coming in.
谢谢你能来
But you're right.  I don't think I will need  to be calling you.
你说得对  我想我不需要给你打电话了
You think you know my story
你们以为知道我的故事？
because you ran  a background check
就因为你做了背景调查
and made a couple  of phone calls?
还打了几个电话吗
I knew yours when I shook  your well-moisturized hand.
当我握着你湿润的手时，我就知道你是谁了
Thank you for your time.
谢谢你抽出时间
I get it. I do.
我明白的  我懂
Who's going to hire  a diagnosed schizophrenic  with a history of violence,
谁会雇佣一个有暴力史的精神分裂症患者呢
when there's  a dozen candidates out there  with sparkling clean records?
尤其是外面还有十几个拥有漂亮简历的求职者
But what's really on my mind  is if I can't get a job,  I can't pay rent this month.
但是我脑子里想的是如果我找不到工作，这个月我就付不起房租了
I mean, dry-cleaning this suit  wasn't exactly free.
我是说，干洗这套西装也不是免费的
And more than that,  I've gotta get something  together real quick,
更重要的是，我得赶紧准备点东西
because these meds,  they're running out.
因为这些药快用完了
And once they do,  shit gets real.
药一旦用完，就该吃屎了
Are there things  you just know how to do?
有没有什么事情是你天生就会的？
Like, no one's  ever showed you.
就像，从来没有人教过你
Somehow each step  in the process makes sense.
但不知何故，这个过程中的每一个步骤都很合理
Like you're remembering it.
就像你一直记得它一样
Not learning it.
但从没学过
For reals, you really  made that shit yourself, man?
说真的, 这真的是你自己制造的吗，伙计
Yep.Damn.
是的
Hey, yo, Ronny.  Yo, Ronny.
嘿   哟  罗尼   哟   罗尼
Evan, man.Hey.
埃文    伙计   嘿
As requested.
专门定制
Kimotsuki-styled iron.  Handcrafted.
日式风格  纯手工打造
One of a kind.
独一无二的
Oh, hell, yeah.
哦   我操    欧耶
Hattori Hanzo, yo? Ooh!
服部半藏是吧
Damn.
我操
Goddamn.Nice.
我了个操   不错哟
Get off me.
别挡着我
Now, let's get this man paid.
现在，付钱给这个家伙
You get high off this shit?
这玩意能让你兴奋？
No. Clozapine.  It's an antipsychotic.
不，氯氮平 是抗精神病药
You get paid in pills?
拿药支付给你吗？
Evan here's on "Ronny-care."
埃文当这里是“罗尼关怀”节目
Yeah. Dr. Ronny.
是的，罗尼医生
Why don't you, like,  get them at Duane Reade?
你为什么不去杜安·里德那里买呢？
Because Evan don't  wanna talk to shrinks  every two weeks. Right?
因为埃文可不想每两周就跟心理医生谈一次 对吧?
Yeah. Evan can't afford  400 bucks a month  on a scrip.
是的 埃文可付不起一个月400块的生活费
Yo. Wikipedia.
哟  维基百科
What's the capital  of "Brakina Fatso"? Yeah.
布拉金纳法索的首都是哪里?  啊？
It's pronounced  Burkina Faso. Ouagadougou.  Could I have my pills, please?
正确发音是布基纳法索  首都是瓦加杜古  能把药给我吗?
Shit, man.  Forgot my count, man.
该死    伙计  忘了数了   伙计
You made that up.
你瞎编的
Damn, man!
我操     伙计
Nah.
那
Homeboy knows everything.  He a freak.
老乡什么都知道   真是个怪胎
How do you know so much?
你怎么知道这么多?
Honestly, I wish I knew.  Makes me nuts.
老实说，我也希望知道怎么回事
Could I have my pills, please.
请把我的药给我
Dang, girl.  You eyeballin' my boy  like he a steak dinner.
小婊咂  你盯着我老弟就像苍蝇盯着牛排一样
Yo, yo.  What's gunpowder made of?
哟  哟  火药是由什么制成的?
74% potassium nitrate,  13% charcoal.
74%硝酸钾，13%木炭
Okay.Damn. Impressive, man.
OK   我操  牛逼啊 伙计
I said eyes on me.
我说了看着我
Come on, Ronny.
拜托  罗尼
There you go, man.  Sixty packages.
给你，伙计 60包
That's only 55.
这只有55
For real?
真的吗?
Close enough.
差不多了
The hell it is.  I live on those.
见鬼去吧  我就靠这些活着
Sixty. Hey.
60包  嘿
Hey.
嘿
You want the real thing,  right? That is it.
你想要真家伙，对吧?  这就是
That's folded over 70 times.  Carbon-treated steel.
折叠锻打70多次  碳处理钢
Take your damn hands off me.
把你该死的手拿开
You better tell your boy  to learn how to count.
你最好让你老弟学会数数
The deal is for 60 bags.
成交价是60包
Yeah?  Well, that's all we got.
是吗? 好吧，我们只有这些了
You don't like it,  you can go back to Bellevue.
如果你不喜欢，你可以去贝尔维尤医院拿
Get the gat on homeboy.
拿了药就滚  老乡
I wanna test this shit out.
我想试试这把狗屎太刀
Yo, what's gunpowder  made of?
哟   火药是什么做的?
Hold out your arm.
伸出你的胳膊
Showtime.
好戏上演
Get up.
起来
Put your arm there, huh?  It's the neck or arm, baby.
把你的胳膊放那儿，嗯?  脖子还是胳膊，宝贝
You choose.
你来选
Hey, Ronny.  That's not a toy, bro.
嘿   罗尼   那不是玩具   兄弟
Mind your business, Evan.
少管闲事，埃文
Come on, Ronny.  This ain't funny.
拜托，罗尼    这一点都不好玩
Oh, God!  My fingers!
哦   上帝!   我的手指!
I think it works,  huh, Ronny?
我觉得这刀还行，是吧，罗尼
Cut my goddamn fingers off, man!
你切断了我该死的手指，伙计!
You'll be all right.  Hey, sweetheart,  why don't you head on home now.
你会没事的  亲爱的   你为什么不现在就回家呢
You're trippin', bro.
你死定了   兄弟
You are done, homey.  You're a dead fool.
你完了，兄弟  你真是个大傻瓜
I don't know, Ronny.  You're talking to a guy
我不知道，罗尼 你在和一个病人说话
who buys antipsychotic  medication from you.
一个跟你买药的精神病人
I'm feeling  a little unbalanced  right now.
我现在感觉有点不平衡
Maybe the best way  to get the voices in my head  to stop talking
也许  让我脑子里的声音停止说话的最好办法   就是砍掉你的脑袋
Do you think it would help?
你觉得那样会有帮助吗?
No. Don't fight.  Don't shoot.  It's cool.
不，别打了   别开枪  要冷静
We're cool, man.  We're cool. All right?
我们很冷静   伙计    我们很冷静    好吗？
Hey, dickhead.  Grab my pills. Now.
嘿，白痴   拿上我的药   快点
There you go.
给你
You're crazy, man.
你疯了,老兄
If I was crazy,  I'd have chopped you up in  little pieces a long time ago.
如果我疯了，我早就把你砍成碎片了
Give me my pills.
把药给我
Now, you listen to me, Ronny.  I'm not crazy, okay?
现在，你听我说，罗尼   我没疯，好吗?
Mm-hmm.I'm just misunderstood.  All right?
嗯，我只是误会了 好吗？
Help!Leona!
救命   丽安娜
Oh!
哦!
NYPD picked up  an Evan McCauley.  Drug deal gone south.
纽约警察逮捕了埃文·麦考利 毒品交易失败了
Cops found a sword on him.
警察在他身上发现一把刀
Blade was made with a process
刀片是用日本江户时代就失传的工艺制造的
So?
所以?
He claims he forged it himself.
他声称是他自己锻造的
Another broker-turned-hipster  blacksmith.
另一个经纪人变成了时髦的铁匠
Oh, ye of little faith.  Are you seeing this, Nora?
哦，你这个小信徒 你看到了吗，诺拉？
Treadway?Precisely.
崔德维   正是
If we know, Bathurst knows.
如果我们知道了，巴瑟斯特也会知道
Be careful.
小心
Thanks, Mom.
谢谢   老妈
Tell us  when you're done, sir.
完成后告诉我们，先生
Can I get my phone call?
我能打个电话吗?
Supposed to get  a phone call.
应该会接到一个电话
You're dressed way too nice  to be an NYPD detective, so...
你穿得太漂亮了，不像是纽约警局的警探，所以…
must be a doctor.
一定是个医生
Not a thing?
认不出？
No recognition at all?
一点都认不出来吗？
I think  I should feel hurt.
我想我应该感到伤心
Do you remember... Syracuse?
你还记得……锡拉库扎
Syracuse.
锡拉库扎
The siege.
全面围攻
Second Punic War.
第二次布匿克战争
Where we first met.
我们第一次见面的地方
Well, not quite the thrill ride  of the First Punic War,
不像第一次布匿战争那样惊险刺激
but, hey,  sequels are tough, huh?
但是，嘿，续集很难，嗯？
You disappoint me.
你让我失望了
Well, join the club.
好吧，加入失望俱乐部吗？
I notice...
我注意到...
you didn't sign it.
你没有签名
Then again...
再说一遍...
craftsmanship like this...
像这样的手艺...
you didn't need to, did you?
你并不需要 ，是吗？
I made a sword.  Is that a crime?
我做了一把刀   这犯法了吗？
Evan McCauley.
埃文·麦考利
Diagnosed with schizophrenia  at 14...
14岁时被诊断为精神分裂症...
after carving the words  Look inside
就在小刀在胸口刻上“看里面”的字样之后
Electroshock proved unhelpful.
电击治疗 无济于事
But these...
但这个...
are not bad, eh?
效果不错，是吧?
Doctor, can I--Please. Go ahead.
医生,我能...   --- 请吧  别客气
At 16, attempted suicide  via car crash,
16岁时，试图通过车祸自杀
necessitating the steel plate  in your skull.
导致你头骨上被钉上钢板治疗
Spent the rest  of your early life
你早些年的生活  是在精神病院和寄养家庭之间徘徊
Well, I only cut  a couple of his fingers off.
嗯，我只割下了他的几根手指
I don't think I'm gonna need  to plead insanity on this one,  am I, Doctor?
我想我不需要为这件事辩护，是吗，医生？
I'm curious.
我很好奇
Look inside.
看里面
Why those words?Why not?
为什么是这几个字？  ---为什么不是呢？
Which one of these...  is yours?
哪一个… 才是你的？
You can skip the--  whatever the hell this is
你可以跳过--- 不管这是什么
because none of that  is mine.
因为这些都不是我的
You're not supposed  to have that in here.
你不应该把那个放在这里
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事?
Hey, Officer.
嘿，警官
Hey, what the hell  is going on here?
嘿，这到底是怎么回事?
Pick it up.
捡起来
What?
什么?
Paris.
巴黎
1794.
1794年
The last meal  of the Comte d'Anjou.
安茹伯爵的最后一餐
A Bordeaux.
波尔多葡萄酒
Not a bad choice  for a last meal.
作为最后一餐，还不错
Was it yours?
是你的吗？
I wish I knew  what you were talking about,  but I don't know what to tell--
我很想知道你在说什么，但我不知道该说什么---
Jesus!
天哪！
Every time you say,  I don't know,
每次你说  我不知道
this trigger  gets pulled.
这个扳机就会被扣下
Is it yours?I don't know--
这是你的吗?   ---我不知道,
Are you out of your mind?
你疯了吗？
We're in a police station!  Hello! Officer!The room is soundproof!
我们在警察局!  喂!  警官!  ---这房间是隔音的!
They won't even hear it  when I put 250 grams of lead  through the back of your skull.
就算我用250克铅弹打穿你的后脑勺 他们也不会听到
Is it yours?Yes. Okay, yes, it's mine.
它是你的吗?    ---是的  好吧，是我的
Are you happy?
你高兴了吧?
Jesus!
我操
Lying... won't help.
说谎... 是没有用的
Look. I'm just a guy  who was at the wrong place  at the wrong time. That's all.
听着，我只是一个在错误的时间出现在错误的地方的人，仅此而已
Last chance, Evan.
最后一次机会，埃文
Is... it... yours?
是... 你... 的...吗?
There's the Treadway I know!
这才是我认识的崔德维
Little trick I learned from you.
小把戏 我以前跟你学的
Hello, old friend.
你好,老朋友
Whoa!
哇!
Get in!
上车!
Hold on.Shit!
坐稳.  ---我操!
Go! Turn! Turn!
快! 转弯!  转弯!
Oh, shit!
哦, 我操!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇!  哇!  哇!  哇!
Go! Go!
快 !   快!
Inside!
在里面
Hold tight.Oh, sh...
抓紧
What are you waiting for?  Come on, let's go!
你在等什么？快点，快点走！
Go the other way!Take the wheel.
走另一条路！你来开车
What? Get out of the car!
什么？
Yeah, sure.  Retractable steering wheel.  No problem. That's normal.
耶，好的   可伸缩方向盘   没问题   这很正常
Reverse.Shoot that son of a bitch.
倒车，射杀那个狗娘养的
Move! Clear the street!
快走！清理街道！
Shoot the driver!
打那个司机！
Jesus Christ!
上帝啊！
Who are they?
他们是谁？
Relax, it's bulletproof.
别紧张，这是防弹的
180 now!
调头  马上
Don't stop.
别停下
Can I ask you a question?Yeah, sure.
我能问你个问题吗？---当然
Who the hell are you?
你到底是谁？
I'm Nora Brightman.
我是诺拉·布莱曼
Okay. But who was  that dude back there?
好吧   但那家伙是谁？
Bathurst.  You didn't recognize him?
巴瑟斯特 你没认出他来吗？
No, I didn't.  But clearly you did.
不，我没有   但很明显你认得
Well, you've known him  a long time.
好吧   你认识他很久了
I've never seen that man  before in my life.  Him, I think I'd remember.
我这辈子从没见过那个人     他，我想我会记得的
Well, not in this life,  maybe.
好吧，也许今生不会
Oh, no. Maybe I bumped into him  during the Second Punic War?
哦，不  也许我在第二次布匿战争中碰到他了？
Or maybe it was  the French Revolution.  I'm bad with dates.
或者是法国大革命     我不喜欢约会
You remember that?No. I don't remember  the French Revolution.
你记得那个了？ --- 不，我不记得法国大革命了
I figured it out.  I see now. I get it.
我想明白了  我现在明白了 我明白了
You do?None of this is real.
是吗？  ---这些都不是真的
It's a psychotic break.
这是精神病发作
I'm gonna wake up  in a hospital somewhere,  drooling all over myself,
我会在某个医院醒来，流着口水
strung out on lithium.Is that easier to believe
浑身都是锂电池    -----虽然这更容易让人相信
than the idea that maybe  destiny has something  more in store for you?
但是命运会为你准备更多的东西
Destiny? Where I come from,  we got bills to pay,  rent to make.
命运？在我的家乡，我们要付帐单，要付房租
Nobody's got time for destiny.That's a shame.
没有人有时间去面对命运    ---真可悲
I know you've been  looking for answers,  Evan.
我知道你一直在寻找答案，埃文
But you're not crazy.  You never have been.
但你没发疯  你从来没发疯过
No, I'm not crazy.  I'm just delusional.
不，我没疯 我只是在妄想
Do you ever find yourself  drawn to places  you've never been?
你有没有发现自己   被吸引到从未去过的地方？
Do you ever see  a picture of a place  and just know you've been there?
你有没有看过某个地方的照片   就知道你去过那里？
Do you know things  you shouldn't?
你知道不该做的事吗？
Do you pick up things fast,  almost as if
你学东西的速度快吗，就好像
you're remembering skills,  not learning them?
你天生就会，而不是学习来的？
I've told  a dozen therapists this.
我已经跟十几个心理医生说过了
I've been analyzed  every way possible,  a hundred times over.
我已经被分析过无数次了
It doesn't mean anything.
这没有任何意义
Do you dream  in other languages?
你用其他语言做梦吗？
[speaks Russian,  Japanese]
[说的是俄语,  日语]
That's what schizophrenia is.  Different people, same head.
这就是精神分裂症   不同的人格  共用同一个脑袋
What if it were  the same person,  different lives?
如果是同一个人，不同的生活呢？
You're talking  about reincarnation.Yeah.
你说的是转世  ---是的
You can forge a sword  because you were  a blacksmith.
你能锻造一把刀，因为你前世是个铁匠
You speak Russian  because you were Russian.
你会说俄语 是因为你前世是俄国人
Look, I hate to break it to you.
听着，我不是在故意打击你
It's a comforting idea,  souls moving from one body  to the next.
这只是一个脑洞大开的想法，灵魂从一个身体转移到另一个身体？
But it's basically just  a spiritual equivalent of  better luck next time. Okay?
但这基本上只是心灵上的一种寄托  好吗？
Nothing more and nothing less.
不会多也不会少
Feel safe warm and inside  all that cynicism?I do, actually.
在冷嘲热讽中感到安全温暖吗?  --- 的确   是的
And how's that  working out for you?In the grand scheme of things?
而这给你带来了什么?    ---从大局来看?
Like big-picture shit?  Not so great.
像屎一样的大局?  没有什么了不起
But I'm good. I'm surviving.
但我很好  我活下来了
The visions you've had  your entire life, Evan,  aren't hallucinations.
你这辈子看到的幻象，埃文，并不是幻觉
They're memories.
它们是你的记忆
So, you're saying  that a hundred doctors  were wrong?
所以，你的意思是 上百个医生都错了？
Fifty medications didn't work  because I'm really a  reincarnated Russian blacksmith?
服用过50种药物都不管用，就因为我真的是一个转世的俄罗斯铁匠
This is real.
这是真的
I'm real.
我是真实的
Oh, yeah? This is  no version of reincarnation  I've ever heard of.
哦，是吗？这不是我听说过的转世版本
Buddhist, Hindu, Sikh.
佛教徒、印度教、锡克教徒
They believe each life begins  with a clean slate.
他们相信每一个生命都是从一张白纸开始的
The answers you've been  looking for all your life...
想知道你一生都在寻找的答案吗
all you gotta do  is get on that plane.
你所要做的就是登上飞机
You know what I'm really  asking myself right now is?
你知道我现在真正想问自己的是什么吗？
What if the craziest thing  I've ever heard--  and this is some crazy shit--
如果这是我听过的最疯狂的事    而且这些疯狂的屁事
is actually  the first thing that's  ever made any goddamn sense?
实际上是我以前从未听过的最合乎情理事 怎么办
I don't gotta go feed the cat,  so... let's go.
反正我也不用去喂猫，那么...走吧
Go on.
继续
They left  from a private airport.
他们从一个私人机场出发
It was an unlisted flight.
这是一次未登记的航班
She was there fast.
她很快就到了
Too fast.
太快了
The sword hadn't been  in the system  for more than a few hours.
这把刀在系统里已经有几个小时没用了
Then they have a base  here in New York.I want it found.
他们在纽约有个基地 我要找到它
It will lead us  to Evan McCauley.
它会带我们找到埃文·麦考利
He will lead us  to the Egg.
他会再一次带我们去找到那个蛋
We call ourselves  the Infinite.
我们称自己为无限
Less than 500 souls  from across the globe,
有不到500个来自世界各地的灵魂
all born with the ability  to remember all our past lives
大家都有能力记住前世的生活和技能
and the skills we've learned  in each of them.
以及在每一个方面都学到的新技能
There are two groups  within the Infinites:
无限内部有两个组织
Bathurst and the Nihilists,  who just want the world to end,
巴瑟斯特和虚无主义者  他们只想毁灭世界
and us... the Believers.
还有我们... 信徒们
And what is it  that we believe?
我们信仰什么？
We believe that our gift  is a responsibility.
我们相信我们的天赋是一种责任
That it's up to us  to leave humanity
让人类变得更好是我们的责任
I think  I'm gonna need these.
我想我该吃药了
Hey.Hey.
嘿   ---嘿
Thanks.
谢谢
Wow. It's a long way  from Arthur Avenue.
哇  离亚瑟大道很远了
It always blows  my mind.
它总是让我大吃一惊
We call it the Hub.
我们称之为中心
This is the place  where you're gonna get  your memories back, Evan.
这是你要找回记忆的地方，埃文
We'll be landing soon.
我们马上就要着陆了
Recognize anything?I'm pretty sure  I'd remember this.
意识到什么了吗?  ---我很肯定我会记得的
It used to be dedicated  to scientific research.
它过去一直致力于科学研究
Anthropology and linguistics.
人类学和语言学
All of us using  what we've learned.
我们都在运用所学知识
Life after life  for the advancement  of mankind.
为了人类的进步，一生又一世
And what is it now?
现在又是什么呢
Headquarters  for the losing side  in the war.
战争中失败一方的指挥部
Bathurst is the master  of combat.
巴瑟斯特是战斗大师
Hundreds of lifetimes.
他转世了上百个轮回
You must be prepared  for everything.
你们必须做好一切准备
He's the apex predator  in our world.
他是世界上最顶尖的掠食者
Again.
再来
Why are they bowing?
他们为什么鞠躬？
They're hoping  you're Heinrich Treadway.
他们希望你是海因里希·崔德维的
Again!Reincarnated.
又一次转世
Heinrich?
海因里希?
It was a popular name  in the '50s.
这是50年代流行的名字
In the '50s.
在50年代
Great for rock 'n' roll,  but lousy for names,  I guess.
很适合摇滚，但名字很烂，我猜
The 1750s.
是18世纪的50年代
What do I know  that you need so bad?
我怎么知道你需要什么？
That's why you're here--  to find out.
这就是你来这里的原因  为了找到答案
This is Treadway's room.Are you asking me  or telling me?
这是崔德维的房间   ---你是在问我还是告诉我？
I must've really screwed up  on my last incarnation.
我上一个化身肯定搞砸了
Why would you say that?
你为什么这么说
Have you seen where I live  in this life?
你看到我这辈子住在哪里了吗？
That's Treadway's  Himalaya diary.
这是崔德维的喜马拉雅日记
That was me.
那就是我
When I was Leona Warrick.
当我还是丽安娜·沃瑞克的时候
And that was Treadway.
那就是崔德维
Two days after that picture  was taken,
照片拍完两天后
Treadway saved my life.
崔德维救了我的命
There's a reason  you picked that book.
你选那本书是有原因的
All this tells me  is what he did.
这些东西都告诉我  他做了什么
None of it tells me  who he was.
但却没有一样能告诉我他是谁
Here we can study  anything and everything.
在这里我们可以学习任何知识技能
Space, time, scale.  It's all relevant.
空间，时间，尺度   一切都是相关的
That doesn't seem  like much.
这似乎不算多
Welcome to my virtual sandbox.
欢迎使用我的虚拟沙盒
Name's Garrick.Hi.
名字是加里克， 嗨
Garrick is our head  of technology and research.
加里克是我们的技术和研究主管
He doesn't  look like much.
他看起来不怎么像
Goddamn, it's good  to see you again.
该死，很高兴再次见到你
It's nice to meet you too.
我也很高兴见到你
Don't worry.  All this shit,  it just gets weirder.
别担心 这一切，越来越诡异了
Okay.
OK
Now let's get started.
现在我们开始吧
Follow me.
跟我来
Stand there for me,  please.
请站在那儿等我
Okay.
OK
That's the guy  from the police station.
是警察局的那个人
Bathurst.  He and Treadway  were once friends.
巴瑟斯特 他和崔德维曾经是朋友
A dozen lifetimes.  Wars, peace.
十几辈子的战争，和平
They stood together at  some of the greatest moments  in human history.
他们在人类历史上最伟大的时刻站在一起
Then Bathurst lost faith.
后来  巴瑟斯特失去了信仰
For the last 300 years,  he's been looking  for a way out.
在过去的300年里，他一直在寻找出路
He needed a way  to stop reincarnating.
他需要一个停止转世的方法
He wants it all to end.
他想结束这一切
That's why he made this.
所以他做了这个
The Egg,  designed to kill every  living thing on earth.
蛋，用来杀死地球上所有的生物
That seems a little drastic.
这似乎有点过激了
If there's nothing left alive,
如果没有活着的东西
there's nothing left  to reincarnate into.
就没有可以转世的东西了
It attacks life  at the source-- DNA--
它从DNA的源头攻击生命
unwinding the very fabric  of existence.
解开一切生存的本质
Every plant, every animal  every person.
包括每种植物，每种动物，每一个人
Mama!
妈妈
Jordan!
乔丹
I'm coming!
我来了
Like unplugging a computer
就像当一个程序死机时
when a program freezes.
拔掉电脑插头一样
Only when he pulls this plug,
只有当他拔掉这个插头
seven billion people  will go with him.
70亿人才会跟他走
Everything it kills  accelerates the process.
它的每一次杀戮都会加速这个过程
God! Holy shit,  that felt freakin' real!
天啊！我了个去，那感觉太真实了！
Without you, none of us  would be here right now.
如果没有你，我们现在谁都不会出现在这里
What are you  talking about?
你在说什么？
Last cycle,  you raided Bathurst's lab,
上一个轮回，你突袭了巴瑟斯特的实验室
stole the Egg,  killed his Einstein and  everyone who helped build it,
偷走了蛋     杀死了他的爱因斯坦和所有参与制造它的人
leaving him with no way  to recreate it.
让他无法再创造它
You took the secret  of the Egg's whereabouts  to your grave.
你把蛋的秘密藏在你的坟墓里
Bathurst spent  this entire lifetime  looking for it.
巴瑟斯特花了一辈子的时间来寻找它
And he's getting closer  and closer to finding it  every day.
他一天天地越来越近了蛋的下落了
That's why he  tracked you down  in New York.
所以他才在纽约找到你
So I get on the plane,  you get all my memories back,
所以我上了飞机，你找回了我所有的记忆
and I save  the whole entire world,  right? That's it?
我拯救了整个世界，对吧？就这样？
That's pretty much  basically it, right?
基本上就是这样，对吧？
Told you it was  gonna get weird.
告诉过你会很诡异的了
So, what now?
那么，现在怎么办？
Tell me good news, Nora.
告诉我点好消息，诺拉
Bryan Porter.  Treadway had a gift  with steel, didn't he?
布莱恩·波特 崔德维有打铁天赋，不是吗？
Impeccable. Your friends  in the NYPD were certainly  impressed with it.
无可挑剔  你在纽约警察局的朋友肯定对这印象深刻
Unfortunately,  their encryption skills  are less than impeccable.
不幸的是，他们的加密技术并不完美
Led us right to you.
把我们引向你
You do know we have easier ways  of doing things now, right?
你知道我们现在做事有更简单的方法，对吧？
Newer...
更新的...
almost never means better.
不会意味着更好
We're going to uncover  Evan McCauley's location.
我们要找出埃文·麦考利的位置
We'll brute-force  your encryption.
我们会用蛮力破解你的密码
But I'd consider it...  a courtesy...
但我会考虑…...用比较礼貌的方式...
if you just...
如果你只是...
sped the process up.
加快了进程
Tell us where he is.
告诉我们他在哪里
Okay.
OK
I know where he is.
我知道他在哪里
Of course I do.
我当然知道
I know exactly where he is.  I just...
我确实知道他在哪里 我只是...
I, um...
我     呃...
I sometimes have difficulties...
有时我的记忆力...
with my memory.
会有点困难
Memory.
记忆力
I remember
我记得
when you used to  gather honey
你曾经在马拉松赛场上
on the fields  of Marathon.
收集蜂蜜
Just another reminder  of how nothing  stays the same.
只是再次提醒你  没有什么东西是一成不变的
Would you care  for some?
你要来点吗
You know what  real torture is?
你知道什么是真正的折磨吗?
Listening to you?
听你说话?
Real torture...  isn't physical pain,
真正的折磨……不是身体上的疼痛
but human stupidity.
而是人类的愚蠢
Being surrounded by it,  engulfed in it.
被它包围，被它吞没
Lifetime after lifetime.
一辈子又一辈子
People with their  idiot grins!
那些傻笑的人
Their infuriating  pleasantries!
他们愤怒的玩笑
Their need for approval!
他们需要被认可
Their unctuous attempts  to be loved and validated!
他们为了被爱和被认可而做出的虚情假意的尝试
They are walking,  talking obituaries...
他们在散步，...在一份倒闭报纸的封底上 谈论讣告...
at the bottom of a birdcage,  in the corner of  a filthy living room
在一个鸟笼的底部,  在一个肮脏的客厅的角落里
of a hoarder cat lady!
一个爱养猫的女人
And we are forced...You'll never understand...
我们被迫…               ---你永远不会明白...
...to live amongst them over......friendship, love.
...在他们中间生活...... ---友谊，爱情
...and over endlessly.
...而且没完没了
That is the true...You still don't understand  about faith!
这就是真相…       ---你仍然不了解信仰
...definition of torture.
...酷刑的定义
Faith! Blah, blah, blah!
信仰！巴拉，巴拉，巴拉
Faith!
信仰!
Faith.
信仰
I'm tired of faith.
我厌倦了信仰
God must show me  his face.
上帝一定要给我看看他的脸
But thank you...  for enlightening me.
但还是谢谢你    谢谢你启发了我
You kept  his fucking body?
你们还留着他该死的尸体
Sexy son of a bitch,  isn't he?
性感的坏蛋,  是不是?
No. He's a dead guy  floating in water.
不，他就是个漂浮在水里的死人
That's pretty much  my worst nightmare.
那几乎是我最可怕的噩梦
Actually,  it's a crotonic acid matrix.  Keeps the cells alive.
实际上，这是一种巴豆酸基质  能使细胞保持活力
Oh. That makes it  that much better.  Thank you.
哦   这让他看起来好多了  谢谢你
We're trying to understand  the science behind what we are.
我们正试图理解这现象背后的科学
Treadway believed  that humans are capable of  so much more than we realized.
崔德维相信人类的能力远比我们意识到的要多得多
Is this what  you're telling me? I'm not  living up to my potential?
这就是你要告诉我的吗？我还没有完全发挥我的潜力?
I've heard that speech before.
我以前听过那个演讲
Treadway pushed  past boundaries others might  call paranormal, superhuman.
崔德维突破了别人可能称之为超自然、超人类的界限
He can manipulate the energy  of the world around him.
他可以操纵周围世界的能量
I don't even know  what that means.
我甚至不知道这意味着什么
What it means  is you'll have skills
这意味着你将拥有超能力
beyond anything  you've ever imagined.
超出你的想象
Those abilities  are very deep.
那些能力隐藏得很深很深
Below the conscious level.
在潜意识之下
I'm down.  How do we get them back?
我倒下了  我们怎么把他们弄回来？
Here,  we retrain your memory.
在这里，我们将重新启迪你的记忆
We combine the physical  and the mental to develop  new neural pathways.
我们结合身体和精神 来开发新的神经通路
Memories are held  in every organ...
记忆存在于你身体的每个器官和细胞中
Regression takes  the kind of concentration  it takes years to develop.
记忆回归需要的是那种需要数年才能培养出来的专注
This is a shortcut.
这是一条捷径
We shock your mind  into synching with the system.
我们会让你的思维与系统同步
It's working.  I'm seeing increased activity  in all his memory centers.
它起作用了  我看到他记忆中心的活跃度在增加
Hey!
嘿
Come on.
来吧
That's not Treadway.Really?
那不是崔德维  ---真的吗？
He just beat you.
他刚刚打败了你
Treadway would've killed me.
崔德维会杀了我的
Wow. She wasn't kidding  about being at war, huh?
哇   她不是在开战争玩笑吧
Improving  the human condition.
改善人类状况
Sometimes you do it  by painting  a chapel ceiling.
有时你可以通过粉刷教堂天花板来实现
Yeah. And sometimes  you drop them  from a mile out.
是啊 有时你会把它们从一英里外扔下来
Don't touch that.
别碰那个
Okay, okay.
OK     OK
That's no gun  I've ever seen before.
那不是我以前见过的枪
We're reverse-engineering  Bathurst's Dethroner.
我们在对巴瑟斯特的废黜者进行逆向工程
A Dethroner?  I mean, dude, who's  coming up with these names?
废黜者? 我是说，老兄，谁会想出这些名字？
Look...
瞧...
you can't kill an Infinite.  You kill the body, but...
你无法杀死一个无限者   你可以消灭肉体,  但...
And they get reincarnated?Yeah.
他们转世了？是的
This implants in your head
这个子弹会植入你的头脑
and pulls out  your consciousness...
把你的意识和灵魂拉出来...
your soul,  and onto a digital chip.
并存放到一个数字芯片上
Your soul gets stuck on a disk  and breaks the cycle.
你的灵魂被卡在磁盘上，循环就被打破了
Over 200 of our brothers  and sisters are lost
我们的兄弟姐妹中曾有200多人
in that digital purgatory.
在数字炼狱中迷失了方向
You come face to face  with this,
要是有一天你面对同样问题
my advice--  find a way to die  the old-fashioned way.
我的建议是：找一种体面的死法
Come in.
进来
Okay if I look around?
我想四处看看
Be my guest.
请便
These are all you,  aren't they?
这些都是你 ，不是吗？
They're people I once was.
她们是我的过去
All of them.
所有的都是
Wow.
哇
That's cool.  You look happy.
太酷了  你看起来很高兴
I was.
是的
Who's that guy?
那家伙是谁？
In that picture,  he was Abel.
在那张照片里，他曾经是亚伯
Before then,  other names, other faces.
在那之前，他有过其别的名字，别的面孔
But the soul...
但是灵魂...
the soul was always him.
灵魂永远是他
So, what?  You loved each other  through multiple lives?
所以, 怎样?  你们彼此相爱了好几辈子?
These are all  the same place.
这些都是同一个地方
Angkor Wat.  What we call the Beginning.
吴哥窟   我们称之为开始的地方
I'll find you in the Beginning.
我会在一开始找到你
I love you.
我爱你
When each of us  would find ourselves  in a new life,
当我们各自都发现自己进入了新生
this is where  Abel and I would go.
这就是亚伯和我要去的地方
You're reincarnated.  How would you know  where to go?
你转世了 你怎么知道去哪儿？
Most of us have a reawakening  that begins young.
我们中的大多数人在年轻时就开始觉醒了
Starts with small things,  memories,
从小事开始，回忆
feelings about a place,  dreams.
对一个地方的感受，梦想
By puberty,
在青春期后
most Infinites  have full recall.
大多数无限者都有了完整的回忆
Right around  the time they diagnosed me  schizophrenic.
就在他们诊断我患有精神分裂症的时候
So what happened  if you died young  and got separated?
如果你们英年早逝，又失散了怎么办
For an Infinite...
作为一个无限者...
death isn't the end,  it's like...
死亡并不是终点   就像...
turning the page in a book.
翻开书页一样
Next chapter, same story.
进入下一章节，还是同样的故事
That's crazy.
太疯狂了
New lives, new bodies,  always meeting back  at the same place.
新的生命，新的身体，总是在同一个地方相遇
He was Dethroned.
他被废黜了
He's trapped  on a computer  somewhere.
他被困在某个电脑里
My last life,  I got my memories back...
上辈子，我找回了记忆...
and realized he was gone.
可是却发现到他不在了
It's not my memories  that matter, Evan.
重要的不是我的记忆，埃文
It's yours.
是你的
Your last life,  in Mexico...
你的前世，在墨西哥...
where did you hide the Egg?
你把蛋藏在哪里了？
Where's the Egg?
蛋在哪里了?
Where is it?
在哪里？
He's spiking.Shut it down.
他过载了   关掉它
Hey, you're okay.
嘿    你还好吗？
You're okay. Hey.  Hey, just breathe.
你没事了   嘿    嘿   深呼吸
I need to get up.Breathe.
扶我起来     ---呼吸
Kovic, check his vitals.
科维奇，检查他的生命体征
What happened in there, Evan?  What did you see?
里面发生了什么，埃文？你看到了什么？
Your neural network fired off  like the Fourth of July.
你的神经网络就像国庆日一样沸腾了
I've been seeing this stuff  all my life. It still  doesn't make any sense.
我一辈子都在看这些东西  却仍然毫无头绪
Why can't he  remember anything?
为什么他什么都不记得了？
Between the car accident,  the electroshock
经历了车祸、电击
and the steel plate in his head,  his mind is fractured.
和他头上钉的钢板，他的精神崩溃了
Something in there  won't let the memories flow.
里面有些东西不允许记忆流动
I can't get them out.  I'm afraid the Artisan  is our last hope.
我无能为力   恐怕工匠是我们最后的希望了
He'll achieve recall soon.
他很快就会回忆起来的
If he hasn't already.
如果他还没有
Hundreds of lifetimes,
数百个世代
and it all comes down  to these few hours.
而这一切都归结到这几个小时
If we don't find him...
如果我们在他恢复记忆之前找不到他...
we lose the Egg...
我们就会永远失去了蛋
The wheels keep turning
车轮不停地转动
and we can never...
我们再也不能...
escape.
逃避
We go at dawn.
我们黎明时出发
It's been a while, Otto.
好久没见了，奥托
No one's called me  by that name in...  so many lifetimes.
这么多世代以来，都没人叫过我这个名字了...
Hello, my love.
你好，我的爱人
What happened to you?
你怎么了?
You were so beautiful.
你曾经是如此的美丽
As were you.
你也是
You don't miss it--
你本应该很 --
the agility...
敏捷...
the vibrancy...
有活力...
being confined to this?
可现在却这样?
You see me  as something broken.  I don't.
你把我看成是残缺的人   但我没有
You're the cripple, Otto.
你是个残废，奥托
Crippled by your cowardice.Cowardice?
懦弱使你残废     ---懦弱?
No. I'm crippled  by my memory.
不    是我的记忆才让我残废的
You get your memories back  over years. Not me.
多年来你找回了记忆    可我没有
I get it all back  as my brain forms.  In the womb.
当我的大脑在子宫里刚刚形成的时候，我就把记忆都提取出来了
Endless hours,  days, weeks, months.
无尽的小时,  天数, 星期, 月份
No room to move!
无法动弹
Nothing  for my brain to do
我的大脑除了吞噬自己什么都做不了
All these lifetimes,  the magnitude of this gift,
这么多世代,  如此重要的天赋
and you haven't  learned a thing.
而你什么都没学到
I have to get out.
我得走了
I have to make it stop.
我必须阻止它
Don't do it.  Don't give him anything.
别这样  什么都不要告诉他
Where is Treadway?
崔德维在哪?
We storming the beach  at Normandy?
我们要搞诺曼底登陆吗?
You never know  with the Artisan.
你和工匠永远都不知道
Let's get ready.
让我们准备好
So, the Artisan's  a gambler?
那么，工匠是个赌徒？
No, he's a hedonist.
不，他是个享乐主义者
Infinite lies,  infinite opportunity  for debauchery.
无限的谎言,  无限的堕落
Sounds like  my kinda guy.
听起来就像我一样
Alexa, music off.
亚历克斯，音乐关了
Get him cleaned up  and outta here.
把他弄干净然后离开这里
You're operating  on dead guys now?
你现在在给死人做手术？
Da Vinci used to  cut into human cadavers
达芬奇过去常常把人的尸体切开
so that he could  better understand  the human form.
以便他能更好地了解人体的结构
For me, I'm all about  that brain, baby.
对我来说，我只关心大脑，宝贝
But you know that  all too well.
但你很清楚这一点
Oh, what a beautiful  cranial arch you got  this time around.
哦，这次你的头骨真漂亮啊！
I could better examine it  if I severed your head  from your neck.
如果能把它从你的脖子上切下来，那我就可以更好地检查它
Like Treadway did to me  when last we met.
就像上次我们见面时崔德维对我做的那样
Try it.Oh.
试试看     ---哦
Bathurst took the Hub.
巴瑟斯特攻占了中心
Does he have the Egg?No.
他拿到蛋了吗?  ---没有
Think we'd be here  if he did?
想想 如果他拿到了，我们还会在这里吗
Wherever it is,  it's still in his head.
不管蛋在哪里，它仍然在他的脑海中
Treadway?
崔德维?
So they say.
正如他们所说
Wait. Is he blocked?
等等    被他锁住了吗
Well, well, well,  look at this.
好吧，好吧，好吧，看看这个
Huh.
嗯
So, your hard drive  got fragged,
所以你的“硬盘”坏了
which means we're gonna  have to reset your memory.
这意味着我们要重置你的记忆
And, Heinrich, I gotta tell ya,  I'm really gonna enjoy this.
还有，海因里希，我得告诉你，我真的很痴迷这个
Ooh!
哦
Check this out.
看看这个
You're all familiar  with the idea  that when you die,
你们都知道当你死的时候
your life flashes  before your eyes, right?
你的生活会在你眼前闪现，对吧？
This machine  enhances that experience,
这台机器增强了这种体验
prolonging  your sense of time,
还延长你的时间感
allowing you  to restore or reorder  everything inside.
允许你恢复或重新排序里面的一切
This-- This right here  is the closest you're gonna get  to a total mental reboot.
这个-- 这个是你最接近于 完全重新启动大脑的地方
Are you planning  on trying to drown me?
你打算淹死我吗？
Cause I got a thing  about drowning.
因为我有一个关于溺水的故事
Which is?I don't like it!
哪个故事?  ---我不喜欢
What kind of success rate  is this guy working with,  anyway?
不管怎样，这家伙的成功率是多少？
Confidence is... high.
把握程度... 很高
Yeah, and so are you,  obviously.
是啊，很明显，你也是
Okay. Hey.
OK    嘿
I like you this time around.  You're actually funny.
我喜欢这辈子的你  你真有趣
Don't take this the wrong way,  but you're usually  kind of a jerk.
别误会，但前世的你通常都是个混蛋
It's true.Yeah, she gets it.
他说得对  --- 啊  她知道的
So, I'm supposed  to trust this guy?
所以，我应该相信这个家伙？
I wouldn't.First,
我不信  ---首先
I resent  the gender labeling.
我讨厌性别标签
Second, you can trust  that we share the same goal.
第二，你可以相信我们有共同的目标
Really? Which is?
真的吗？是哪个？
Bathurst wants to what,  destroy every living thing  on Earth?
巴瑟斯特想要什么，毁灭地球上所有的生物？
Well, that's gonna ruin  a pretty great party  I've got goin' on here.
那肯定会毁了我正在办的一个很棒的派对的
This guy's out of his mind.  Hey--
这家伙疯了   嘿
There's a reason you  didn't bring me here before.Mmm.
你之前没带我来是有原因的
I could die in there.Yeah.
我可能会死在里面      ---是的
Could it work?
它能成功吗？
It could.
必须的
But you have a choice,  Evan.
但你可以选择的，埃文
No, I don't have a choice.
不，我没有选择
I... I can't let  anybody else get hurt
我…我不能让任何人因为我脑子里的东西而受到伤害
All right.  Leap-of-faith time.
好吧  信仰要飞跃了
Let's just do it now  before I change my mind.  All right?
在我改变主意之前，我们现在就开始吧  好吗
Let's go.  Turn your machine on.
开始吧   打开你的机器
Ooh. Ready to go for a swim?
哦  准备好去游泳了吗？
Yes.  This is gonna be so fun!
对   这会很有趣的！
Just shut up and turn it on.
闭嘴，把它打开
..prolongs your sense of time.
..延长你的时间感
Whatever happens,  don't let them stop  until it's done.
不管发生什么事，在完成之前不要让他们停下来
He'll hold his breath  as long as he can, and then...
他会尽量屏住呼吸，然后...
base instinct  takes over.
本能会接管一切
Oh, my God.  He's drowning.
哦，天哪 他快淹死了
That's the whole idea.
这就是整个想法
Maybe we should pull him out.He's not there yet.  Two more minutes.
也许我们应该把他拉出来  他还没到达   再等两分钟
Abel, listen to me.  If I fail...
亚伯，听我说  如果我失败了...
Come on.
加油
Nora...He's dying.
诺拉…   ---他要死了
We're close.  We are close.
就快好了   就快好了
Doesn't have a pulse!
没有脉搏了
Get him out!
把他弄出来
Come on!  Come on.
快点   快点
Okay. Okay.
OK    OK
Get out of the way.
快闪开
No!
不
He's gone.
他死了
We killed him.
我们杀了他
If I fail, look inside.
如果我失败了，看里面
Evan, you're okay.  Just breathe.
埃文，你没事了  呼吸
I am Treadway.  I am Treadway.
我是崔德维  我是崔德维
I'm Treadway.
我是崔德维
If you are Treadway,  answer this:
如果你是崔德维，回答这个问题：
Do you know  where the Egg is?
你知道蛋在哪里吗？
Yes.
是的
Yes?Yes.
是吗?   ---是的
Look inside. Look inside.
看里面     看里面
We were trained  to think of bodies  as unimportant, right?
我们接受的训练  让我们认为身体不重要，对吧
Right.Just shells  meant to be discarded.
是的   身体只是一副能随意丢弃的躯壳
Well, Treadway knew  the one place
崔德维知道，有一个没人会去看的地方
Abel? Abel, listen to me.
亚伯  亚伯  听我说
If I fail, look inside.
如果我失败了    看里面
It's in his body.
就在他的身体里
Back at the Hub.
回到中心去
It's been there  the whole time.  Come on.
它一直都在那里   快点
I am shocked that that worked.
我很震惊  这居然奏效了
I knew it was you  the whole time.  That's why I let you win.
我一直都知道是你  所以我才让你赢
Oh, you let me, huh?
哦，你让我的，是吗？
Whoo! I don't know  about you guys,
喔！我不知道你们什么情况
but I could use a drink.
但我想喝一杯
Come on,  we don't have time for--
快点，我们没时间玩了--
Security lockdown!
安全封锁！
I'm hit.
我中弹了
You all right?
你没事吧?
Hey!
嘿
Follow me.
跟我来
Come on. We gotta go.
快点   我们得走了
Open emergency lift.
开启应急电梯
We gotta go. We gotta go.Wait!
我们得走了    我们得走了   等等
Are you crazy?  They're about to breach!
你疯了吗？他们就要破门而入了
We're not running,  all right?  I'm tired of running.
我们不跑了，好吗？ 我厌倦了逃跑
I'm gonna fight 'em right now. Hang in there, Trace.
我现在就要和他们战斗   ---坚持住，翠丝
She's dead.
她死了
Guys, we need to leave now.
伙计们，我们得马上走了
I'm staying.What?
我要留下  什么？
We stay here,  we fight 'em now.
我们要留在这里，现在就和他们战斗
You're leaking  like the Titanic.I'm fine.
你就像泰坦尼克号一样漏水   ---我很好
If you die here,  who stops Bathurst?
如果你死在这里，谁能阻止巴瑟斯特？
He's right.
他说得对
Hey.
嘿
You make this worth it,  dziecko.
你让这一切都值得了，迪齐科
Then buy me some time.
那就给我争取点时间
Open weapons room door.
打开武器室的门
Good luck.
祝你好运
Careful, sir.
小心点，先生
Oh, I will be.
哦，我会的
We're taking  Treadway's body  to Scotland.
我们要把崔德维的尸体带到苏格兰去
Very well.
非常好
Keep him alive.
让他活着
I'll do the best I can,  but he's lost a lot of blood.
我会尽力的，但他失血过多
The keys are in the car.
钥匙在车里
Heinrich.
海因里希
Good of you to join us.
很高兴你能加入我们
I only wish  you were here  to see this...
我只希望你能在这里看到这个场景...
to understand your...
来理解你...
your role in this.
在这个过程中的角色
The end of all our debates.
我们的辩论到此结束
The end of all things.
万物的终结
Have it cleaned and tested.
拿去洗洗再测试
Make sure  it's the real thing.
确保它是真的
Is it really over?
真的结束了吗？
Not quite yet.
还不至于
Never underestimate  Treadway.
永远不要低估崔德维
Ah. You're awake.
啊 你醒了
Where am I?
我在哪?
I told Nora  I'd wait with you  until you woke up.
我告诉诺拉  我会和你呆在一起，直到你醒来
You're in my safe house.
你在我的安全屋里
What are you doing?I'm doing your morphine!
你在干什么？ ---我在给你注射吗啡
Where is she?
她在哪？
Huh?  Oh, she went after Bathurst.
嗯    哦，她去追巴瑟斯特了
Oh, shit.
哦  糟糕
She's not doing this alone.  No way.
她不能一个人去  没门
Whoa, whoa!  Come on, man.
哇   哇   拜托  伙计
You try running out now,  you'll bleed out  before you reach the compound.
如果你现在跑出去，在到达营地之前你就流完血了
If we're going down,  we're going down together.
如果我们要完蛋，那我们就一起完蛋
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
嘿    嘿    嘿    嘿
I just patched you up, man.
我刚帮你包扎好，伙计
Let me catch you up  on the current situation.
让我给你介绍一下目前的情况
If Bathurst gets his way,  we're all done.
如果巴瑟斯特得逞，我们就完了
There's no more  second chances.
再也没有第二次机会了
I'm gonna get the Egg  and kill him.
我要去抢蛋   然后杀了他
She told me you were one of us.
她告诉我 你是我们中的一员
Obviously,  you're just full of shit.
很明显，你只是满嘴狗屎
Diagnostics are done.  The bomb is ready for the Egg.
测试完成了  蛋里的炸弹也准备好了
Have them load it  on the plane.
让他们把它装上飞机
Come here, you bastard.
过来，你这个混蛋
Do you think He'll...
你认为上帝会 ...
let us do this?
让我们这么做吗?
No?
不会?
The end of all things.
万物的终结
Go.
走
Move, move, move!On the rig! Let's go!
快，快，快！上车！快走 ！
Move, move!
快，快 !
Dropping in three, two, one.
准备投放  三   二   一
Do you need a ride?Love one.
你需要搭车吗？  ---我喜欢
You okay?No. Don't ask.
你还好吗？  ---不，别问了
Did you see that?
你们看到了吗？
Nora, you okay?
诺拉，你没事吧？
I got you.
我扶你
I'll get you out of here.  Come on.
我会带你离开这里的    来吧
You all right?
你没事吧？
Oh, shit.
哦  糟糕
Hey. We gotta get you  out of here.
嘿。我们得离开这里
You gonna be okay to move?Yeah, I'll be fine.
你还能动吗？   ---是的，我会没事的
Okay. Come on.
OK  加油
You gotta go.Bathurst is getting away.
你得走了   ---巴瑟斯特要离开了
His hard drives are here.  I have to destroy them  and free them all.
他的硬盘在这里 我必须消灭他们，把他们全部解放
I'll see you again.
我会再回来找你的
We'll be landing in Glasgow  in 16 minutes, sir.
我们16分钟后在格拉斯哥着陆，长官
Stay low.
飞低一点
Use TFR.
使用TFR
Oh, my God.
哦   我的天
Come on. Come on.
快点   快点
They're all here.
他们全都在这儿
All the souls.
所有的灵魂
We have to free them all.
我们必须把他们全部解放
Whoa!
哇
Nora. Nora, hey. Hey.
诺拉  诺拉  嘿  嘿
Stay with me, okay?  We are so close.
别离开我，好吗？我们快成功了
Let's blow some shit up,  huh?
我们来炸点东西吧
Shit!
糟糕
We've lost engine three, sir.
我们失去了三号引擎，长官
We're gonna have to  land the aircraft.
我们得让飞机降落
What the hell  are you doing? Sir!
你到底在干什么?  长官
Please! You're gonna  crash the aircraft. Sir!
拜托! 你会让飞机坠毁的 长官
It's impossible.
这是不可能的
I-Impossible.
不 - 不可能的
He's opened  the bloody top hatch, sir.
他打开了该死的顶部舱门，长官
You disappoint me.
你让我失望了
No recognition  whatsoever, huh?
“什么都认不出来，”嗯？
I think I should feel hurt.
“我想我应该感到伤心"
Car crash?  Steel plate, remember?
车祸？钢板，记得吗？
Treadway,  you can't deactivate it!
崔德维,  你没法解除它了
It's happening!
没机会了
No!
不
Death isn't the end.  Not for us.
对于我们来说  死亡不是终点
Maybe not for any of us.
对我们任何人来说都不是
New chapter, same story.
新的篇章，同样的故事
I can carry you out.
我可以抱你出去
No way.
没门
I'll free them.
我要解放他们
Here.
给你
I'll see you around.Yeah.
来生再见  好的
I'll find you in the Beginning.
我会在一开始的地方就找到你
I love you.
我爱你
I ask myself...
我扪心自问...
what did being Evan McCauley  teach me?
成为 埃文·麦考利 教会了我什么？
If each new life  is a chance to build  on what was,
如果每个新生命都是一个建立在前世基础上的机会
a chance to press forward  to the best of what could be...
一个向最好的方向前进的机会...
...why will some of us  have to pick up the sword  and fight again...
...为什么我们中的一些人要拿起剑再次战斗...
...while others discover  a new beginning?
...而另一些人却发现了一个新的开始？
Nora?
诺拉?
It's hope.  That's what I learned.
是希望  这就是我所学到的
Yes, we fall.  Yes, we fail.
是啊，我们跌倒了  是啊，我们失败了
Yes, sometimes we screw up  everything we touch.
是啊，有时候我们会把碰到的每件事都搞砸
But each moment we live  is connected by a belief
但我们生活的每一刻都被一种信仰联系在一起
that the actions we take will  next day, next week, next life
我们所做的事将在第二天，下周，下辈子发生
add up to something more,
多积累一些比你自己更重要的东西吧
And next... well,  the possibilities are...
然后  ... 好吧,  机会将是...
infinite.
无限的
So...
所以...
when your son  starts asking questions  about his past,
当你儿子开始问起他的过去
give me a call.
给我打个电话
He says he's just a child. Ehh...
他说他只是个孩子   呃...
What about your sword?
你的刀呢？
Artisan,  what took you so long?
工匠，你怎么这么久？
See you soon, Treadway.
再见，崔德维